Guide to the Frank H. T. Rhodes papers,1977-1996.
Rhodes, Frank H. T. papers, 1977-1996.
- Series XV. 1991-1992
  - Presidential/Administrative
    - Board of Trustees
      - Trustee Committees, 1991-92 (Box 259, Folder 27)
      - Academic Affairs Committee, 1991-92 (Box 259, Folder 28-29)
        Fraternity discipline; Alcohol policy.
      - Board Membership Committee, 1991-92 (Box 259, Folder 30-35)
      - Buildings and Properties Committee, 1991-92 (Box 259, Folder 36-38)
      - Corporate Liaison Committee, 1991-92 (Box 259, Folder 39)
      - Development Committee, 1991-92 (Box 259, Folder 40)
      - Development Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 1-6)
      - Investment Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 7-12)
      - Proxy Review Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 13)
        Gleitsman, Alan L.; Tobacco divestment.
      - Committee on Land Grant and Statutory College Affairs, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 14)
      - Advisory Committee on the Status of Women, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 15)
      - Trustee Meetings - General, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 16)
      - July Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 17)
      - September Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 18-19)
      - October Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 20)
      - October Board, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 21-23)
      - November Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 24)
      - December Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 25)
      - January Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 26)
      - January Board, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 27-28)
        CUMC Recruitment of Women and Minorities.
      - February Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 29)
      - March Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 30)
      - March Board, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 31-33)
      - April Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 34-35)
      - May Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 36)
      - May Board, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 37-39)
        UAW video on Cornell Employees.
      - June Executive Committee, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 40)
    - university assembly
      - General, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 41-42)
        Bicycle regulations.
      - Employee Assembly, 1991-92 (Box 260, Folder 43)
      - Student Assembly, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 1-7)
        Dean of Students Office; Palmer, Larry I.; Transient Vending.
      - Codes and Judicial Committee, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 8)
      - Hearing and Review Boards, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 9)
      - Campus Planning Committee, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 10)
      - Assembly Leadership, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 11)
  - Provost's Office
    - Office of the Provost
      - Spring Budget Meetings, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 12)
      - Deans' Council Agendas, 1990-92 (Box 261, Folder 13-15)
        AIDS policy.
      - Academic Deans' Agendas, 1986-92 (Box 261, Folder 16-17)
      - Precinct Planning, 1990-91 (Box 261, Folder 18-20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 21-22)
        Jones, Thomas W.; Retention of Latino administrators; Students indicted for computer virus; Reflections on the Sixties and the Nineties; Modern history of Cornell.
      - Senior Provost, 1987-91 (Box 261, Folder 23-24)
        Barker, Robert; Undergraduate course enrollment; Space planning; Undergraduate experience; Land grant mission.
      - 8 Provosts' Meetings, 1986-91 (Box 261, Folder 25-26)
        Underrepresented minorities in science; Indirect costs; Sexual harrassment; Mandatory retirement; Animal testing.
      - General, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 27)
        Porter, Brian; Hate crimes; Quill and Dagger discrimination against minority student activists.
      - General, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 28)
        Financial conditions; Rhodes Scholarship.
      - Accessory Instruction, 1986-90 (Box 261, Folder 29-30)
      - Donors, 1988-92 (Box 261, Folder 31)
        LaFeber, Walter; Dyson, John S.; Dickstein,
      - Accounts, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 32-34)
        Federal Express; Telephone; Campus store.
      - Calendar, 1991-92 (Box 261, Folder 35)
        Petition for amendment to final exam schedule.
      - Campus Code of Conduct/ Budget, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Provost Emeritus, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Academic Personnel, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 3)
        Academic layoffs.
      - Enrollment, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Admissions, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 5-10)
        Murphy, Susan H.; Legacy admissions; Financial aid policy; Recruitment; Associate dean search.
      - Admissions Study, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 11-12)
        Institutional planning; Possibility of centralized undergraduate admissions.
      - African Development Institute, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 13)
      - Biological Sciences, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 14)
      - Isle of Shoals, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 15)
      - Financial Aid, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 16)
        Sheinkman, Jack.
      - International Student Financial Aid, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 17-18)
      - Student Employment, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 19)
      - Cornell Tradition, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 20)
      - Mario Einaudi Center for International Studies, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 21-27)
        International curriculum development; Peace studies program; SCOLA; Hispanic American Studies Program Director search; Piedra, José.
      - Indirect Costs, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 28-35)
        Stanford university report; Cornell expenditures; Naval Research.
      - Peace Studies Program, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 36)
        Peace Studies review.
      - Cornell Abroad, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 37)
      - Area Studies, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 38-39)
        Near Eastern Studies; Southeast Asian Studies; Soviet Studies; Latin American Studies; Minority protests of financial aid cuts; HASP protests and student demands.
      - East Asia Program, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 40)
      - International Students Office, 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 41)
      - Higher Education Opportunity Program, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 1)
      - Minority Education, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 2)
      - Native Americans, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 3)
        Akwe:kon.
      - Science, Technology and Society, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 4)
      - Summer Session/ Extramural, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 5)
        Altschuler, Glenn C.
      - Cornell Adult University, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 6)
      - Minority Affairs, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 7-10)
        Graduate fellowships; Comprehensive Human Resource Development Program; Commitment to Diversity; Atlantic Philanthropic Service Co.
      - The Michigan Mandate, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 11)
      - Affirmative Action, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 12-13)
        Faculty Recruiting.
      - Civil Rights Complaints, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 14)
      - Report of the Visiting Committee, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 15)
      - Minority Resources and Issues, 1989-91 (Box 263, Folder 16-18)
        Visiting Committee; Start Smart Program.
      - Tuition, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 19)
      - Graduate Tuition Committee, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 20)
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 21-23)
        Springfest; Random freshman housing assignment; Graduate student assembly; taeching assistant training; Recruitment.
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 24)
        Barcelo, Lucy; Silicano report on alcohol policy.
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 25)
        Classroom scheduling.
      - Career Center, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 26)
      - Center for Religion, Ethics and Social Policy, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 27)
      - Cornell United Religious Work, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 28)
        Sage Chapel Preaching Contest.
      - Dean of Students, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 29-31)
        Ford, John L.; Kramer, Howard C.; Housing; Alcohol Policy; Parents Survey.
      - Cornell University Press, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 32)
      - Dining, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 33)
      - Health Careers, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 34)
        Preveterinary majors.
      - Housing, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 35-37)
        Turner, James E.; Freshman housing crisis; Faculty in Residence; Greek living facilities; Random freshman housing controversy.
      - Fraternities and Sororities, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 38)
        Dyson, John S.; Discipline.
      - Ujamma, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 39)
      - Johnson Museum of Art, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 40)
        Overton, Warner; Art Director search.
      - Ornithology Laboratory, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 41)
      - Learning Skills Center, 1991-92 (Box 263, Folder 42)
      - Cornell in Washington, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 1)
        Boehner, Carol.
      - ROTC, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 2)
      - Registrar, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - Undergraduate Education, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 4)
        Parents Survey; Merrill Presidential Scholars.
      - Graduate Student Life Committee, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 5)
      - Libraries, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 6-7)
        Seznec, Alain; Space needs.
      - Undergraduate Complaints, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 8)
      - University Unions, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 9)
      - Africana Center, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 10)
      - Solid Waste Combustion Institute, 1988-92 (Box 264, Folder 11-13)
        Indemnification.
      - Total Quality Management, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 14)
        Corporate challenge; CESR-B Factory.
      - National Nanofabrication Facility, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 15)
      - Vice President for Research, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 16-17)
      - Biotechnology, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 18)
        Jelinski, Lynn.
      - Arecibo, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 19-21)
      - Astronomy, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 22)
      - Center for Environment, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 23)
      - CLEARS Review, 1988 (Box 264, Folder 24)
        Ballantyne, Joseph M.
      - CISER, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 25)
      - Materials Science Center, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 26)
        Sponsored Programs.
      - Theory Center, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 27)
        Funding.
      - Vice President for Information Technology, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 28-30)
        CIT Relocation; Academic Integrity; Students indicted for computer virus; Computing Board; CUBIT.
      - National Conference of Student Diversity, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 31)
      - Vice President for Human Relations, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 32-35)
        Diversity on campus; Human Resources Development Council; Pre-freshman program; Allegations of Quill and Dagger discrimination; Disabled; Office of Equal Opportunity.
      - Sexual Harrassment, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 37)
      - Sexual Assault Prevention, 1991-92 (Box 264, Folder 38)
      - The Crisis of Minority Faculty at Cornell, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 39)
        Cohen/ Gates Report.
      - Vice President for Planning, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 1)
      - Institutional Planning, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 2)
        Graduation rates.
      - Space Utility and Assignment, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 3)
      - Provost Support - State Programs Account, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 4)
      - Japanese Gift Studies Account, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 5)
      - Special Provost Account, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 6)
      - Mellon Grant Account, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 7-8)
        Fresh Combinations Program.
      - MacArthur Foundation Account, 1985-90 (Box 265, Folder 9-10)
        International Security Program; Peace Studies.
      - John S. Fair, Jr. Fund Account, 1987-91 (Box 265, Folder 11)
      - LeRoy Grumman Fund Account, 1987-91 (Box 265, Folder 12)
      - Reappropriation Savings Account, 1987-91 (Box 265, Folder 13)
      - Senior Provost Expense Account, 1990-91 (Box 265, Folder 14)
      - Egner Project Account, 1987-91 (Box 265, Folder 15)
        Egner, Joan R..
      - W. D. Cooke Emeritus Professor Account, 1987-91 (Box 265, Folder 16)
      - Weiss Contingency Fund Account, 1987-91 (Box 265, Folder 17)
      - Academic Recruiting Account, 1988-91 (Box 265, Folder 18-19)
      - Provost - General Account, 1988-91 (Box 265, Folder 20-21)
    - Colleges
      - Statutory Affairs, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 22-25)
        State budget reductions; Doctoral meeting; State and Cornell TIAA/CREF contributions controversy; Bress, Joseph M.
      - Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 26-28)
        Agricultural Economics strategic plan; Teacher Education in Science and Mathematics.
      - CIIFAD (Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture and Development), 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 29)
        BIFADEC (Board for International Food and Agricultural Development and Economic Cooperation); Dominican Republic cooperation.
      - New Faculty Appointments, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 30)
        Taylor, Dorcetta.
      - Programs, 1991-92 (Box 265, Folder 31)
        Cooperative Extension; Industrial Extension; Cornell Plantations; Sea Grant Institute.
      - College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1990-92 (Box 265, Folder 32-33)
      - Economics Review, 1990-1992 (Box 265, Folder 34-36)
        Provost's Committee on Economics at Cornell.
      - Economics Review - Provost's Committee on Economics, 1990-1992 (Box 266, Folder 1-3)
      - Provost's Committee on Economics - (Files added later - came from another office), 1991 (Box 353)
      - Economics Review - Curricula Vitae of Faculty, 1990-1992 (Box 266, Folder 4-8)
      - College of Arts and Sciences, 1991-1992 (Box 266, Folder 9-10)
        Military recruitment; Knight Writing Program.
      - College of Arts and Sciences, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 11-13)
        Gates, Henry Louis, Jr. (Skip); Kohlstedt, Sally G.; Cognitive Studies; Music Department; Sogah, Dotsevi; Language Resource Center.
      - College of Arts and Sciences, 1990-92 (Box 266, Folder 14-16)
        Lowi, Theodore J.; Statistics Center; Theatre Arts Department; Council of the Creative and Performing Arts.
      - Society for the Humanities, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 17)
      - College of Engineering, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 18-21)
        Attrition among Black engineering students; Sexual harrassment case.
      - Geological Sciences, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 22)
        Allegre, Claude; Turcotte, Donald; Karig, Daniel.
      - Graduate School, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 23-25)
        Graduate Advocacy Organization; Summer funding; Organization.
      - Big Red Barn, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 26-27)
        The Henry graduate center.
      - Graduate and Professional Student Assembly, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 28)
        Grievance procedure for graduate students.
      - Graduate Student Advisory Board, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 29)
        Committee on Graduate Student Life.
      - A. D. White Professors-at-Large, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 30-31)
        Bronfenbrenner, Urie; Delano, Jack.
      - Johnson Graduate School of Management, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 32-35)
      - School of Hotel Administration, 1991-92 (Box 266, Folder 36-38)
        Simon, Augusta; Homeless program; Proposal for a name change to the "Cornell Society of Hotelmen"; Hotel School strategic plan.
      - New York State College of Human Ecology, 1991-92 (Box 267, Folder 1-3)
        Statutory funding reductions; Outreach programming; Beckman, Ronald.
      - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1991-92 (Box 267, Folder 4-6)
        Funding; Ehrenberg, Ronald G.; TIAA/ CREF contribution controversy.
      - Law School, 1991-92 (Box 267, Folder 7-9)
        Military recruitment on campus.
      - New York State College of Veterinary Medicine, 1991-92 (Box 267, Folder 10-11)
        Environmental concerns in Schurmann Hall and the Veterinary Research Tower; Tenure.
      - Division of Nutritional Sciences, 1991-92 (Box 267, Folder 12)
      - Interdisciplinary Programs, 1991-92 (Box 267, Folder 13)
        Scott, Norman R.
      - A Committment to Access, 1991-92 (Box 267, Folder 14)
    - cornell academic background material
      - Abstracts, 1979-92 (Box 267, Folder 15-31)
        Bart, Constance.
    - Long range planning
      - Long Range Planning, 1982-92 (Box 267, Folder 32-37)
        1984Master Plan; Mission statement; Capital planning; High priority projects; Strategic planning; Values statement; Cornell in the Nineties, Cornell at 2000; Ballantyne, Joseph M.
      - Long Range Planning, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files
    - Associations
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 2-4)
      - Association of American Universities, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 5-7)
        Rosenzweig, Robert M.; Presidential search.
      - ACE, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 8)
      - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 9)
      - American Association of University Professors, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 10)
      - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 11)
      - Consortium of Social Science Associations, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 12)
      - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 13)
      - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 14)
        Tuition Assistance Program; Bundy Aid.
      - Education Commission of the States, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 15)
      - Council of Ivy Group Presidents, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 16-21)
        Gender equity in athletics; Elimination of freshman football; K-12 outreach; U.S. v. Brown University, et al.; Antitrust legislation.
      - Middle States Association, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 22)
      - Middle States Association Accreditation Review at Cornell, 1979-92 (Box 268, Folder 23-28)
      - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 29)
      - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 30)
      - TIAA/ CREF, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 31)
      - Universities Research Association, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 32-33)
    - corporations
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 34)
      - Corning Glass, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 35)
      - DuPont, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 36)
      - Emerson Electric, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 37)
      - General Electric, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 38)
      - General Motors Corporation, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 39)
      - Hewlett Packard, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 40)
      - IBM, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 41)
        Cornell Quality Improvement process.
      - Mobil Oil, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 42)
      - Procter and Gamble, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 43)
      - Shell Oil, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 44)
      - Fellowships/ Scholarships, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 45)
    - Foundations
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 46-47)
        Whittaker Foundation; Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust.
      - Prizes and Awards, 1991-92 (Box 268, Folder 48-49)
      - President's Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 1)
      - Atlantic Philanthropic Services Company, Inc., 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 2-6)
      - Exxon Education Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 7)
      - Ford Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 8)
      - Freedom Forum, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 9)
      - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 10)
      - Hewlett Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 11)
      - Keck Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 12)
      - Kellogg Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 13)
      - Knight Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 14)
        Black, Creed; Writing program.
      - Kresge Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 15)
      - Luce Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 16-17)
        Topping, Melissa S.
      - Mellon Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 18-19)
      - MacArthur Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 20)
      - National Science Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 21)
        Massey, Walter E.
      - New York State Science and Technology Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 22)
      - Olin Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 23)
      - Pew Charitable Trusts, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 24-25)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 26)
      - Sloan Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 27)
      - Statler Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 28)
      - Teagle Foundation, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 29)
    - rhodes memberships
      - General Electric Board of Directors, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 30-36)
        Welch, John F.; Boycott; Litigation; Environmental Concerns.
      - Mellon Foundation Board of Trustees, 1991-92 (Box 269, Folder 37-44)
        Project to publish correspondence of Charles Darwin, Charles; Literacy Program; University Libraries.
      - Mellon Foundation Board of Trustees, 1991-92 (Box 270, Folder 1-2)
      - National Science Board, 1991-92 (Box 270, Folder 3-30)
        Commission on the future of the National Science Foundation.
      - National Science Board, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 1-3)
        Commission on the future of the National Science Foundation; Indirect costs.
      - Academy for Educational Development Board of Directors, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 4-6)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 7-8)
        Special membership panel for educational administration.
      - American Philosophical Society, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 9)
      - President's Education Policy Advisory Committee, 1989-92 (Box 271, Folder 10)
      - Committee for Economic Development, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 11-12)
      - Council for Aid to Education, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 13)
      - International Executive Service Corps, 1988-92 (Box 271, Folder 14-16)
        Cornell Capital Campaign; Long Range Planning.
    - Higher Education
      - Department of Education, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 17)
      - General, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 18)
        Roundtable discussion.
      - Bundy Aid, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 20-25)
      - State Education Department, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 26)
      - Title IX, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 27)
        Gender equity in athletics.
    - Universities
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 28-31)
        Plane, Robert; Russian-American Consortium.
      - SUNY - General, 1991-92 (Box 271, Folder 32-36)
        SUNY Master Plan.
      - SUNY - General, 1991-92 (Box 272, Folder 1-5)
        SUNY 2000; SUNY Faculty; Senate; Joint trustee meeting; New degree program proposals.
    - Student Life
      - Student Records Policy, 1991-92 (Box 272, Folder 6)
      - Students - Miscellaneous, 1991-92 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Campus Affairs
      - Incidents, 1991-92 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Commencement
      - Baccalaureate Service, 1991-92 (Box 272, Folder 9)
      - General, 1991-92 (Box 272, Folder 10-12)
        Ferraro, Geraldine; President's Breakfast; Freshman Convocation; Granting degrees.
- Series XVI. 1992-1993
  - Presidential/Administrative
    - Office of the President
      - General, 1992-93 (Box 272, Folder 13-14)
        University College of Swansea.
      - General Correspondence, 1992-93 (Box 272, Folder 15-20)
        Blanchard, Kenneth H.; MacCorkle, Emmett W.; Hatfield, Robert S.; Klein, Daniel P.
      - Condolences, 1992-93 (Box 272, Folder 21)
        Quinn, Terrence.; Cornell, George D.; Marcham, Frederick; Ashby, Lord Eric.; Foley, William T.
      - Congratulations, 1992-93 (Box 272, Folder 22-25)
      - Professors Emeritus, 1992-93 (Box 272, Folder 26)
        Ziegler, Jerome E.
      - Invitations, 1992-93 (Box 272, Folder 27)
      - Presidential Staff, 1992-93 (Box 272, Folder 28)
        Wagner, M. Joy; Bart, Constance; Cook, Constance E..
      - Affirmative Action Unit Representative, 1992-93 (Box 272, Folder 29-30)
        Progress Toward Diversity.